<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers on Mahrokh Ghoddousi Boroujeni</title>
    <link>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Papers on Mahrokh Ghoddousi Boroujeni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.129.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A PAC-Bayesian Framework for Optimal Control with Stability Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/pac-snoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/pac-snoc/</guid>
      <description>This paper presents a novel approach using PAC-Bayes theory to provide generalization bounds for Stochastic Nonlinear Optimal Control (SNOC), enhancing control policy reliability and mitigating overfitting, demonstrated through neural network controllers in cooperative robotics. To appear in the IEEE Conference on Decision and Control, 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Federated Learning of Probabilistic Models: A PAC-Bayesian Approach </title>
      <link>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/pac-pfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/pac-pfl/</guid>
      <description>This paper introduces PAC-PFL, a personalized federated learning algorithm that leverages PAC-Bayesian theory and differential privacy to enhance model accuracy and calibration for heterogeneous clients, validated through experiments on various datasets. Under review.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for Walking and Running of Bipedal Robots</title>
      <link>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/biped/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/biped/</guid>
      <description>This paper presents a framework for generating various walking and running gaits in bipedal robots by using virtual constraints to relax the fixed center of mass height assumption, demonstrated through simulations of the robot Bolt under environmental uncertainties and disturbances. In International Conference on Advanced Robotics, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy of Real-Time Pricing in Smart Grid</title>
      <link>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/dp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mahrokhgb.github.io/publications/dp/</guid>
      <description>This paper proposes using Differential Privacy to protect household occupancy states in smart grids by perturbing electricity rates before publication, demonstrated through a Markov model and tested on data inspired by household occupancy models. In the IEEE Conference on Decision and Control, 2019.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
